hello
my name is poultryman and welcome back
to another episode of hermitcraft and
now today i need to head straight over
to my pet chicken that i adopted sally
because you actually have to look after
it you've got to put a bit of effort in
you've got to like clean it out and
stuff so that's where we're heading
straight away to take care of that
before we crack on with some other
errands that we need to do today it
looks like there's a couple of boxes
around here now
whoa looks like all of them are taken up
oh this is awesome
okay so all the chickens have been
adopted
and my one is in here sally liberated by
poultry man and there there she is i
don't know where all the other chickens
have gone
uh it turns out that i messed up last
time i was here and i put a couple of
slabs here and here and
she got out but fortunately
stress has brought her back so i just
need to do a little bit of cleaning up
it looks still looks really nice here
actually oh no there is sally's got one
friend okay so i need to whoa
oh i didn't bring any shulker boxes
and i didn't bring any quartz you know
if i'm gonna do this i really should
think ahead i've messed up okay i'll be
back in a second with the things that i
actually need in fact why don't i go
ahead and just put this sand
straight in to green's shop here to try
and sell it immediately that will help
him out a massive amount okay i've got
everything that i need and sally has
aged one cycle that means she's now one
years old i can now put in the stack of
nether quartz that i need to feed her
and i can take out all of this from the
litter tray so at the moment it's cost
me 40 diamonds
and i have had that many stacks of sand
so that's still over a diamond per stack
of sand but if sally here survives for
just two or three more years then i'll
get my money's worth if sally here
survives eight years i'll have made a
proper profit on this whole thing and it
will be worth making this this little
thing oh wait i totally thought that was
sally this is sally sally doesn't seem
to move very much he
okay never mind you're okay
all right let's head back now that we've
taken care of sally there's something
else that we need to do oh look at this
this is so sad of course we're going to
make some donations
of course we are we wouldn't leave
someone out to dry poultry man's got
your back escal don't you worry i'm a
true hero on this server and i will
supply you with eggs
ho ho
the tables have turned and now to head
over to the festive district where
things are getting built this was empty
last time i was here i mean uh
last time green told me about it now
where is the secret santa this must be
it
welcome to the secret center place names
in here uh secret santa guide you know
what i should probably read this okay so
let's put one in for me
there we are
and i might put one in for my buddy
green as well
okay so in we go one for green
and what what i must have renamed the
same bit of paper so i've kind of got
some levels there we go
right green and poultry man there we go
and i guess we will both have to draw
our names in the next episode to see who
we get and also we can take an optional
naughty or nice which is going to be
interesting because
if i get someone that's been naughty
they're getting a whole bunch of coal i
can tell you that and that is a hero's
taste oh
ow
i was gonna say that's a hero's job done
i need to put feather falling on these
or something because these are deadly
now last episode some crazy stuff was
going down and i got pranked by
ren and doc right i got pranked really
good like they got me really good it's
super funny
however
it turns out
that
the book here wasn't written by them
okay so i was very wrong in assuming
that it was meant for me which makes
sense right because it's the the prank
wasn't even at my base you thought if
they were going to prank me they would
have at least done it here
so
it turns out that maybe they did do it
but didn't record it but someone wrote a
book and led me there and changed the
signs at cleo's base
so instead of just guessing if it was
clear because i saw so many comments
saying it's cleo clio changed it
i'm just going to go and ask her
straight up whether she was behind this
or not i think that's probably the best
way maybe she's at her base somewhere
let's see if i can get her to come over
here wherever she is
right here you are cleo thanks for
joining me
so you're very welcome
i think you know what i'm going to ask
don't you
i think i i actually do know what you're
going to ask because i would blame me
from that as well i've had lots of
comments you've been accused in the
comments
look
in my last episode someone wrote me a
book in my base that said to come here
now i actually missed this sign
completely i went straight over here
and i went and spanned the key and fell
for it right
oh okay it wasn't until afterwards that
i saw this
well this proves that it was
whoever did this it was meant for me but
we now know that doc and oh
we now know
that
doc and ren
were the ones that made this right and
yes and impulse
and impulse
and import did you not know it was
impulse no impulse too yeah that makes
sense because of the scale of this thing
this is definitely a three-man job i was
given this book that led me here but why
would they put the prank in your base if
it was meant for me
which
in hindsight was really stupid of me
so are you saying that you didn't change
the sign you did i did not change the
site if i was going to change a sign
i would do it on camera and i would
admit to it because it's hilarious
no this was not me well i've been
keeping an eye out and i haven't seen
anyone else take credit for this
no me neither i i want to clear my name
i'm not being funny though but you could
be lying to me right now i don't trust
anyone anymore
don't trust anyone i'm not i'm not i
could be i could very well be lied to
you but i'm not
um you just you either have to trust me
or you don't i have done a little prank
in the meantime though
against ren and uh not against impulse
you must know that i've already
done something
to uh yes i have heard rumors um
i've seen what you've done which is
great by the way so that kind of that
actually covers all the bases then it
does that that covers all three yeah i
dragged tango along and he helped me
prank the stock exchange
and i've got joe and jeff on my side
is that death do i i think are you here
oh yeah i hear death
oh they're your death okay so right let
me get this straight let me just get the
story straight because this i'm not
gonna lie i'm not following all of the
the chess pieces that are in play right
now
i was dragged into this because false
used the prank item with me and then
i've been
i i've been like an unwilling
participant in all this and then i've
been bamboozled using this thing and now
i'm but i can't let things slide i could
have just like let it go but i didn't i
mean you're welcome to come and see what
we've done to impulse just to uh
yeah no that's a good idea can i can i
see what you've done
yeah absolutely come along oh i need to
de-trap it but that's fine yes
so this is the
the prank right this is it yeah this is
this is the uh the hall of atonement for
impulse and of course we want to divest
him of his possessions because it's
funnier that way do you want to take
this apart so you can show me what
you've done i don't want to trigger
anything in here yeah no problem is it
safe to go in
it is safe to go in now
oh it's dark oh my goodness okay
welcome to the attempted murder room
murder is wrong
okay well i don't want to show too much
of this
because i obviously i obviously want to
see what impulse is going to do but
you've you've put him on
so i want to say i'm not going to read
the signs but if you look back here if
you look back here yeah there are
dispensers and we're going to have
cursive binding items applied to his
outfit i've taken the cursive bindings
out oh so that's why you need him to
part with his stuff i got it
all right so i won't i won't spoil any
more because we want to see exactly how
impulse is going to react to all this so
i'm not going to spoil any more of that
than i already did but i i understand
now you're sending him on a story a
story of words to yes joe's words
specifically joe hill's words
those are always slightly into more
entertaining than my words i am i'm very
intrigued to see how this goes do you
think he's gonna feel bad is that the
whole point to it emotionally
yeah let's send him on a guilt trip but
also it's just to make him paranoid sort
of like when is the death gonna poke her
it's gonna occur here no here no yeah if
i touch this button is think something
good
you don't even but you don't even get
him in the end
i get him in this soul which is the main
place no but cleo you don't understand
it's not enough
he killed me okay what i'm saying is i
know a joe might not do this but i i
will
all i'm saying is
all i'm saying is we get a bucket of
lava and we put it here and he won't be
able to get out
if he really does take off all his items
before he goes in he'll be safe and he
will be free of all the curse of binding
stuff but if he doesn't take if he does
take all his stuff he's going to lose
all of his diamond gear he has to trust
you when he goes in what do you think i
mean i'm in i'm not going to tell the
other two either it's so easy as well
like you just put one lava here because
he'll go straight up that water elevator
and it'll be it'll be done you're a
genius at this well done
let's go grab actually i've actually got
a bucket here i just need to find some
lava so is everything now done
everything is now in place it's all set
are you okay with this
i am
impulse will 100 die
he will 100 percent i joe will not be
okay with this but you know what joe
doesn't know doesn't hurt him you are
right there
that's why we need to not tell joe about
this at all but he's not he's still
culpable because he did this as well
this is perfect i've just i've just
taken his linguistic prank and just made
it so crude
[Laughter]
we get both best of both worlds now we
definitely need to prank and they also
died well i i feel like i'm getting
getting even as well but you've got a
really nice ghost ship now which is
awesome but i know that's mine now
they totally would have got you if
someone didn't like lure me in which i
still suspect i'm not i don't know who
it is i'm kind of waiting for some
videos to come out to see if anyone
takes credit for it they haven't left
the note they haven't left a sign and
it's not appeared in any video
so
i think we might be waiting a while so
we don't know well anyway
let's uh let's get out of here before
impulse comes online
[Laughter]
thank you cleo
there is
so much going on now so just by chance i
didn't see the impulse had done it now
that i think about it there was a mob
that had impulse on it but i because i
didn't get the head from the the zombie
that it that dropped i've got ren and
doc's head in here like i've got a
little like
uh chest of evidence here like i got the
treasure room key i've got doc's head
and i got ren's head and a book and
quill that was you know i got all of
that stuff but i didn't pick up
impulse's head so i didn't even think to
to get him so cleo knew
that i'd already got
the ren and doc so she went after
impulse which says to me
that she's potentially an ally
and probably wasn't responsible hear me
out so if clio did indeed put the book
there why would she then go and prank
impulse because she would have just
tried to totally push it off me
would it be possible to invite such a
noble gentleman to a cuppa yeah of
course
okay iskall now wants to invite me for a
cup of tea apparently which is very
unlike iskall
so i'm immediately suspicious i am so
paranoid of everyone now i have no idea
what's going on okay let's let's go meet
up
okay here i am at iskall's base and as
usual there's mobs everywhere hello
green
hello what are you wearing hello sir
oh nothing special i figured if we have
an occasion like this i'd better put on
my best clothes and shaving and days and
all that
what is this
no not nothing at all okay so so i've i
figured such a such a noble gentleman as
yourself that i just want to invite you
for for a little bit of a an english
tradition
afternoon tea
afternoon yes yes afternoon tea exactly
it sounds much better when you say it
afternoon tea
yes absolutely so right over here i've
actually prepared for us oh my goodness
whatever meat thing shall we say why
have you got a everyone's head
here yeah this this is a long story but
there there is a lot of shenanigans
going on at the moment and a man needs
to know his allegiance so i'm just
keeping track you gotta match up the
entire server
yep i'm gonna make sure i know where
things are going down dude my base looks
so cool
it looks like a crosshair or like a
target it looks really cool am i gonna
lie
mumbo's looks like a sorry i'm getting
distracted anyway so you've got uh
tea and toast
yeah so i i figured i'd invite you for
iskale have you ever had afternoon tea
before
i
i i in sweden we we are
you serve scones and jam not toast and
tea
oh okay
well
excuse my ignorance for the for the tea
and toast but you know did you put a tea
bag in this dude it looks it looks
incredibly like water
i've learned from my english experience
that english people usually like it a
little bit light side so
there may not be too much of the tea
baggage in there that was definitely
you you know what's interesting with tea
and toast though
what
because because i've learned as i grew
up that this is this is an english thing
the tea and toast tea and toast how
would you abbreviate t in total screen t
t
t and t
uh tmt tnt
there you go now see here is
my now we're touching on an on an issue
that happened i was wondering where this
was going
right it's a little bit far-fetched but
i had to get your attention and you know
there is no better way of getting an
english person's attention than with
some tea and with some tnt especially
this english there you go
there you go now we're talking
so
you asked about the allegiance of heads
and things and you asked about the map
now i want you to come over here
down where my bases and take a close
look at at the sandy village that you
helped me build um
yeah there's a big uh
like pimples on and a big white square
right next to it exactly
right
so i'll be honest i mapped this entire
thing out today and i did i was so like
caught up in mapping it out that i
didn't pay attention to the fact that my
castle
is completely vanished and replaced with
a cake oh is that what is that what it
is
oh something oh it's a minecraft cake oh
my goodness some minecraft cake okay
wait so that because there's so many
things going on now who did that
so i checked it out and it turns out the
full symmetry yeah
she pranked me
which is fair enough that's why she's
upside down
she's not evil to me okay but you
pranked her she
i pranked her so it's kind of fair
enough she's still you know she's still
she's still evil okay
i mean i mean only good fun but then
there was a sign for mr ren dog as well
which makes no sense to me like i you
know me and reno we we're bros man yeah
but you know cleo changed the sign you
know how that went down cleo changed the
sign from your prank from iskall to ren
so
cleo
did that
and then ren got together with impulse
and doc to prank cleo
this is all really complicated i am it
is that's why i did this room for myself
so i could try and like stay on top of
this thing but what but by the things
you're saying like doc would be
would be with ren here ren is anti-i
mean this is so confusing false and ren
seems to made an alliance to make a
giant cake which you know at first sight
looking at the map i was like that's
kind of interesting but let's let's get
up there let's let let me take okay
you know when you invited me for tea i
was like what is going on here i was
like i was not into this at all like
what is this and then you made me say
tnt and then i was like
oh
you see i invited you for tnt
you know no scones and jam wait do you
want me to blow this up
yeah you see this is made out of dye
right and to be honest with you like
even if my castle is still here i want
to show you something come down here
first before you make conclusions okay
this is this is insane dude so i was
like okay is my castle inside here look
at this this is solid oh they did it
oh my goodness it's not it's it's not
just a shell
it's a full-on solid is your castle
completely gone
no i think i think i hit the wall of the
cat yeah look at this this is where it
goes oh my goodness dude
not enough there not enough there look
here they film
they're insane dude well i can't say
that you don't deserve this
and
i actually saw the chicken earlier and
all the poop was gone they've clearly
reused the poop that you
use the same but wait a minute
the chicken in a green costume did poop
fancy poop because there was white
concrete powder in it
okay so they've just used the diorite
they've just used the diorite wait what
do these signs say
uh the red velvet cake in a demon
costume by ren
you see this is the next thing because i
made like an art piece out of mine and
they've done the same
but okay so yeah i i really really
cannot like
stand this and then i just saw it was
funny because i checked this out and you
log on to the server and i'm like hey
green likes tnt
so okay i was right you want me to get
rid of this for you
i'm thinking you should get rid of this
but you know
if i get rid of this
i can't guarantee the safety of your
castle
i would say the castle is tainted
forever they put too much bird poop on
top of it why do you never want to touch
it why do you hate diorite so much it's
just a block
it's bird poop dude look at it
yeah look at this i mean it's better now
but but you played with the old textures
okay yeah but still it's like is it is
it worth blowing up this entire thing
just because you hate dye alright
let me ask you the question like this
instead okay
would you stare into bird poop in real
life and say it's just bird poop man
whatever okay but would i look into bird
poop and say this is so ugly i need to
blow it up with explosives no no i
wouldn't yeah i would i totally i think
that's fair i think that's that's common
wait are you telling me
that you
you out of all people you wouldn't want
to blow this up no no no what i'm saying
is i wouldn't blow up bird poop with tnt
it's it's totally unnecessary
okay but yeah but this thing yeah i
would totally i i totally blow out this
cake
100 100
good this is going to be glorious uh but
about a payment
uh it's a service
oh yeah
tnt doesn't come cheap
exactly so so now we go back to the to
the little to the little meeting into my
to my i put on fancy clothes for you um
and and i've made you tea and toast are
you saying that's not enough
wait you want me to do this for free
it's not for free really i'm not a suit
guy i really hate this suit i'm in pain
you know that suit looks a little bit
like diorite
it
oh my god
it has its similarity
i shall never wear it again i shall
never wear it again
i hated that white suit
what happened to your hair let's not
talk about the hair it's something that
occurs to men when they get older okay
okay all right okay i've made up my mind
so i will blow this up for you pro bono
you don't no charge but you owe me okay
you owe me you owe me one i don't know
who i can trust anymore and i need some
i need some friends in this whole thing
because
i don't know who i can trust like you i
don't have a wall of of people but i
don't know what's going on much anymore
i kind of know some events
but i don't know everything okay so i'll
blow this up i'm here
but you owe me fair enough yeah okay i
owe you that's scary to accept by the
way but i owe you also i totally would
have done that for free as well so
i'll go grab some tnt
are you ready for this i've got my tnt
always ready okay for tea and toast tea
and toast i love it this is and you're
gr you're great at this like you're not
gonna damage like my village and stuff
for you i mean
uh there's no guarantees um
there's no guarantees refunds or
otherwise terms and conditions
it's you get what you get and that's it
uh as you can see there's some
complicated redstone here we do this
professionally around here okay this is
not a mickey mouse operation
all right it's all ready to go
okay
now
say goodbye to the bird you can do the
honors or shall i
oh
you may is that
[Laughter]
[Applause]
that was feeble
do you see the problem is i was trying
to be conservative
none of that
none of that anymore no we're gonna put
down every bit of tnt that i have yep
it's going get off the glass
oh
my goodness it's glorious
that was a beautiful there we go that's
more like it
um
dude okay wait come here look at look
into my eyes look into my eyes
look into my eyes your castle was gone
before i blew it up
yeah i know
don't blame the demolition man
blame the pranksters
i
i will
and hey i i owe you one seriously i
couldn't have done this there's a lot of
tnt there's like three stacks of tnt in
there
i'm telling you die right yeah like it's
a thyroid isn't evil even three stacks
of tnt can get rid of all this
well that was uh a good job well done
but you know this is a bit of a this is
a bit of a masterpiece i think when it
comes down to it so i think we need to
rename this piece
i um it's not exactly a
this isn't exactly an arty name but it's
true i wouldn't eat this cake if i were
you by korean
what a mess what an absolute mess
but
i think i need to go back to my base and
start working on some stuff because this
is absolutely insane
there's just so much going on now so to
try and keep up to date maybe i should
make like a big wall of trying to keep
up to date i know that doc and ren at
impulse are out to get me
or at least
i think they are cleo is possibly an
ally because she didn't actually want to
lead me into her prank but she did prank
impulse
because i pranked
doc and ren
man this is so confusing
maybe we need to make some sort of big
conspiracy wall thing
but it looks like iskall could be a
friend in all this since he now owes me
and he came to me to get that destroyed
looks like cleo could be a friend and
well of course tango is a friend because
he helped me do the heist in the first
place this looks like
things could get really out of hand or
maybe they already have and i have not
realized it yet but that doesn't mean
that we can't keep working on our base
there's still lots to do here the
general consensus from my last video
was to put some greenery in the base
because it's it does actually look
futuristic
um
however
there was actually quite a lot of people
that said no even though the majority
said yes there was quite a lot that said
no so i thought this section up here in
particular
it doesn't actually have anything in it
and it's not actually a great size to
put anything in it either so what if
this was like
my relaxing room where i made some real
greenery like an aviary in here i could
get some parrots in here some like a
fish pond or something i could make this
really calming in here and this could be
my like relaxation room it's just an
idea that way i could have the greenery
without making it look weird on the rest
of the
i
used the rocket
[Laughter]
unfortunately that is all we have time
for in today's episode hopefully we'll
get a bit more actual work done and stop
getting distracted by this silly war
going on
and it is actually time to draw the
center i know earlier i said we do it in
next episode but it's actually been a
day or two so i can actually draw it out
now
i yeah i drew myself great thanks guys
let's try again
what
let's try again okay no i've messed it
up
all right so i have iskall and has iscal
been naughty or nice
[Laughter]
he's been a naughty
this girl's been a naughty man
brilliant okay so that's it for me
everyone thank you very much for
watching we have interrupted cleo's
prank a little bit i think we've
improved it a little bit so we've
actually got even with impulse who
actually went and killed me we still
don't know who led me into that trap
we also went and helped iskall clear up
his trap
and i've drawn my secret santa as well
things are getting extraordinarily out
of hand and difficult to follow but it's
been really really fun so far and i
can't wait to see where this all goes
anyway thank you very much for watching
and good
bye